I hyperfixate on certain things, particularly things that I want to find a solution about.
So there's certain people who will be like, you know, I have like a real like issue. I had an
interaction with Amanda and, you know, this, you know, like, and it didn't go well. And so I really
do want to create a space called Clear the Air where people can have a conversation with me
about a scenario where they felt like I didn't show up right. Right. And the goal of this is not
even about me, like trying to just be everybody for everyone. But I really do feel like conflict
resolution is a thing that I've definitely gotten better at and that I think that our community could
get better at. But what I learned today in my going against my psychiatrist orders and actually reading
the comments is that some of y'all don't, you don't even want any kind of actual clarity. You just want
to be mollified. They really are just looking for you to humble yourself because if you can't tell
someone what they did wrong, then you have no place to tell them to get right. And if someone is
genuinely asking, where did I make a misstep? And you then say, listen, I'm not going to go through
the back and forth of this. Then what did we really start this for? I think a lot of us have dealt with
this in our interpersonal relationships, but imagine dealing with that with strangers. It's a losing
battle. Ultimately, I don't think it's fair to ask people to take accountability for an offense that
you cannot describe.